

ABOUT ME

647-883-2181

priswongys@gmail.com

% priswongys.github.io

A Toronto graduate and multidisciplinary designer with a passion for all things technology and design related. My career focus is in user interfaces and creating user experiences that people can feel more integrated with and can create an experience that is clear, concise and elegantly smart.

TOOLS

Adobe Photoshop Web & Mobile Interface Design

SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Graphic Design

Adobe InDesign Wireframing

Adobe Experience Design Prototyping

Invision User Flow Creation

Balsamiq Project Management

Moqups HTML/CSS

WordPress

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce [Business Economics]

Ryerson University Sep 2011 - Jun 2016

Qualified for Top 200 Leadership Program due to outstanding academic achievement and extracurricular school involvement.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer

KRFTWRK Jan 2017 - Present

Translated clients' product visions and concepts into wireframes and mockups that lead to intuitive user experiences. Have taken user-centered design approaches to make strategic decisions related to core, and new, functions and features.

Web & Graphic Designer

OutReach Media Apr 2016 - Present

Prepared website concepts for multiple clients, based on business requirements, with responsive design principles in place. Collaborated with design members to prepare for a unison brand identity for the organization.

Web Designer

Mercedes-Benz Canada Dec 2015 - Feb 2016

Organized user flow and designed UI prototypes of the website's revampment that included new features while in line with the company's branding guidelines.

Junior UX/UI Designer

DEMHUB Oct 2015 - Mar 2016

Responsible for the creation of product redesign, user flow, and interaction that developers can execute on to meet end users' needs and company objectives.